Opening Talk!
Yay!
LOL!
You waiting for me?
Waiting?
Why are you laughing?
LOL!
I'm Arisa Saito, and I'll be in charge today!
Please do!
I recently had a chance to perform in a play in June.
I've been performing for a little over a week.
It was my first time, so I was surprised at the rehearsal.
I wore a very frilly skirt on the first day.
I wore something like a blouse with ribbons on it.
But, you know, we have to wear comfortable clothes for rehearsals, right?
So I didn't bring a change of clothes.
I thought, "Oh, I messed up! I thought to myself.
I thought to myself, "I knew I had to wear comfortable clothes for practice.
I thought to myself, "Oh, I messed up.
I thought, "Oh, I messed up.
Was it okay? Did you spread your legs or anything like that?
It was the first day, so I was still fine.
After that day, I started wearing very casual clothes.
I was a little surprised when he said to me.
You look like you're 15 years old.
I'm one year older than everyone else in Rough Rough Rough.
But I'm about 10 years older than everyone else.
I thought that was refreshing.
I didn't want to look like an older sister in Ruff Ruff.
In riffraff, you get licked by Miku and Miri.
They lick me.
I was happy to have that sisterly experience.
Well, Mr. Hoteyson, I'm looking forward to working with you!
Please!
I didn't hear you.
We usually just sit in the akkon and really...
And it's rare that we start with an opening talk.
We're suddenly being chased.
So this is Miku.
Nice to meet you.
Let's start with you, Mr. Sakuma.
Before we go around, Sakuma-san...
You see this T-shirt above?
My daughter gave it to me for Father's Day.
She said, "Your father is going to be on the front page.
I've been giving Mr. Matsumoto a hard time lately.
He thinks I'm a bad guy.
I'm a human being.
That's what he said in the episode.
It made me smile.
Summer means festivals, right? That's right.
I heard that Rough Rough has been asked to play at various festivals this summer.
Oh, that's something.
So, I put together a little more information.
Here they are.
Wow, the number of people.
You're going to play Yokohama Arena?
Yes, we are.
Yokohama Arena.
Yokohama Arena?
Really?Oh, seriously?
That's amazing.
There are probably various stages in the Yokohama Arena.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, maybe.
But it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Is it unusual for a debutante to be performing in such a rocket ship? Mr. Sakuma.
I don't know. I've never produced idols before.
No, no, no.
I've never produced an idol.
So, among many other things, Friday, August 11th is a national holiday.
This is the day of the holiday. I'm not sure what's going to happen,
Well, everyone in Rough Rough already knows what's going to happen.
Now, Mr. Sakuma, please make an announcement.
Yes, I'm going to have a second live concert on this day.
We are going to have a second live concert on this day!
Wow!
It's going to be at Shinagawa Intercity Hall.
Shinagawa Intercity Hall.
This is...
No, it's a little bigger than last time.
What's the capacity?
700.
Wow!
That's a first, isn't it?
We didn't fill 500 alone.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm like, really.
That's awesome!
That's why we have to fill it.
Saito, what did you think?
How did you feel when you heard, frankly?
Last time we had 400 people.
So it's doubled.
I still can't imagine.
I can't even think about it.
It's like it's not realistic.
Like a dream.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
A song about liking yourself, liking yourself, liking yourself, liking yourself
A song to be
Let me shout
Let me cry
Even if I cry
Oops!
You like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you like you
So, what a summer logo for the summer.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Here it is.
Oh!
Nice!
It looks like summer.
Summery.
Is it common practice for Sam's to make a logo for summer?
They are writing songs for summer, and they are going to make costumes for summer.
Oh, I see. So you won't be wearing this outfit anymore?
Yes, yes.
Does this mean winter?
No, this is spring.No, this is spring.
Spring, spring, spring.
I'm sure of it. I know, I know.
Yes, I know.
This time, I would like to send you this project for such an important summer festival.
Summer festival, Kamashian presentation contest!
Yay!
Simply put, just being able to sing and dance is not enough,
So, in order to let as many people as possible know the appeal of Rough Rough, we asked everyone to come up with their own ideas for the Kamashian of the Summer Festival,
What do you think of this?
Do idols usually do that?
I don't know. They don't, do they?
I don't think so, but that's why I was wondering how to get people to remember it.
Kamashi" is too much of a comedian's term, isn't it?
The atmosphere of summer is a little bit...well, you know.
It would be a waste if they could just sing and dance. It's not a waste.
That's for sure.
That's what idols are for, isn't it?
It's totally fine.
It's fine. And, well, you wrote what you actually do.
If there is something really good, let's do it.
Let's do it.
It's good, isn't it?
It's a little bit, what kind of...
People might think we are a little bit different from other idols.
So the atmosphere of the first one-man show was a bit like the "Yinare" show, wasn't it?
It's a nuance like the first one-man show, "Yinare"?
So, I heard that there is a festival next Sunday, and you will be doing it from there as well.
Next week, right?
Next Sunday. The president will do it from the end.
I'm scared.
Hayashi, can you make it?
It's the day before the end-of-term test.
I'm not going to do the final test.
That's great. You're a student. That's great.
If I slipped a lot, it would have a huge impact on the chi-square test.
The chiropractic test.
That's great. And, well, we decided that it would be a little bit, well, you know...
You're so kind, aren't you?
Yes, after all, we are being nice.
This is Mr. Ueda, the official elder brother. Please come in.
Here he is. My brother's brother is an ogre, you know.
But when you get to be Ueda-san's age, you can bring your own chair, which is wonderful.
That's wonderful.
I'm very grateful.
Big brother.
Really. You are like an apprentice child.
Really.
Was he your disciple?
No, well, I'm close to that.
What do you think, Mr. Ueda? Today, you are going to be a judge.
Yes, I am.
You made a lot of negative judgments at the first man-man show.
How do you feel? How do you feel about it?
I am looking forward to seeing what you have come up with, based on the story of the last first live performance.
I hope you will judge me harshly.
Strictly.
Yes, please.
Then, I will be the one to judge. I'll go first.
Hayashi. I'm Hayashi from the Summer Festival Sickle Shop. Please give me time to think about it.
Please give me time to think about it.Please give me time to think about it.
What is it?
There is a song called "Please give me time to think," in which we sing and dance, and then cut off in the middle of the song.
Yes, there is.
Please get mad at producer Sakuma.
I'm Hayashi Figures.
Please stop calling me a junior high school student on All Night Japan!
I'd like to ask the audience for a question for the comedy contest, and then answer it on the spur of the moment.
And incorporate it into a song?
That would certainly give the fans a sense of doing something together!
Put one person on stage, and mic him up.
If you've got a good idea, come on up!
The hearts of the fans are amazing, but...
Let's do this for a minute.
Shogo is the fan.
Hayashi says, "Come on, you've got a good idea, come on up!
I'll do it.
Let's do it!
Whoever has a good idea, come on up on stage!
Hey! Hey, you tasty chazuke!
What is the new Anpanman character that was banned from the airwaves?
It's hard!
He's definitely not confident.
Like, "That's a good question.
It's a good question!
Then answer it!
I'm going to dance one time.
Dancing?
Let's dance.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Answer first!
Tell me the new Anpanman character that was banned from the airwaves.
That's all you say.
Asparagus Taro.
Why?
Because it's green.
That's a great answer!
Why don't you answer the question?
Okay, I'll answer.
Shake it out.
What is the name of the new Anpanman character that was banned from the airwaves?
Zayakpanna.
The fans will win.
No one can beat Zayakpanna.
Are you sure about that, Zayakpanna?
I'll beat you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Wait a minute!
Don't just sit there and answer.
What is the new Anpanman character that was banned from the airwaves?
Dark business pooch.
Say it.
It's a tough match.
One on one versus Porgy
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't let me out to see it
Draw.
But there's a feeling it's going to be interesting.
What do you think, maid?
I have a good feeling that it's going to be tingly.I have a feeling it's going to be a good tingle, so...
Tingling in idle life.
It's rare.
I think it's nice, but don't be satisfied with just this exchange
It's tough, tough.
But you're saying there's a little bit of potential.
Yes, it is.
Well then, let's continue.
Okay, then... Yashimura.
Yes, I'm quite realistic and I'm a little confident.
Throwing an autograph ball
We're going to throw an autograph ball that we've already written in advance.
And we're asking for time to think about it, and it's also a comedy song, but it's a baseball song, and it's about baseball.
So I'll throw it then.
What are you going to write on it?
A sign.
You're going to write the answer to the question on there.
But that's kind of interesting.
That's a good idea.
It's going to be a great memory of the day.
Then the message that fans don't like to be given
A message on a signed ball.
What's the message?
The sound is you, right?
Or that one... I don't need that one...
It's just a roll of tissues.
Oh, man.
It's not the angle I thought it was.
I'm a little concerned about this.
Saito's amazing entrance.
Idol festivals...
At idol festivals, many idols appear in place of each other.
I thought the opening was the most important part of the show.
So I thought the opening was the most important.
I think that's true.
I don't want the people who have come before to leave.
To make them become a fan of Rough Rough.
I think it will be a great success if you make the opening look really great.
I'm sure it would be a success.
I'm sure everyone will be ooh'd and aah'd.
So, I've got an idea.
What? A great entrance.
A ninja run.
All of us.
But if it works, I'm sure it'll be great.
What do you mean?
Hi, Ruff Ruff.
They're ninja-running from over there.
And sit down?
Say, "Hi, I'm Ruff Ruff." Sit down.
Okay, maybe.
Are we sharing? First of all.
You know Ninja Rider?
Uh, Spider Run.
Idol group.
I say keep it low.
Okay, I'll go ahead. I'll go ahead and introduce Ruff Ruff. Come on in.
Hi, I'm Ruff Ruff.
They're not catching up.
I mean, the back's not catching up. I'll lose heart before the back comes out.I'm not catching up with the back of the pack, or I'd lose heart before the back of the pack came out.
The ninja's appearance was embarrassing.
Embarrassing.
I just thought it would be better if he made an appearance like this.
Do you have any suggestions?
If there is...
Oh!
Seino.
There's a guy in the audience.
Ah!
Shota-san's style in the store
This could be good.
Shota-san.
Maybe that's a good place to start.
Shota-san
Today
Might be a good place to start.
That certainly makes sense.
Cocky.
A young idol...
Seriously.
But okay, but it's kinda funny.
Daisho
Well, they're flying in from the sky.
From the sky
Falling. Theta.
You mean he's coming in theta?
So, someone, Arisa, come downstairs to the audience.
Arisa, you come down to the audience.
Come to the audience higher up.
This is still a little difficult to do practically.
It costs a lot of money.
Ueda to change the way of appearance
What do you think?
I think it's not bad.
But I don't want to do it on the assumption that we'll lose.
I don't want to do that.
I see.
You want me to catch it.
Catch the machine.
Yeah, it's a little early to go in the back.
Oh, that's wonderful.
It shouldn't be just for the fans.
Yes, sir.
It should make people laugh.
Make them think, "What's up with these guys?
Fujisaki's Mayhem Bushies...
You mean simple mayhem?
Yes, everyone knows.
That's right.
I thought if we all got together for a mayhem bush...
I thought we could unite.
Oh!
Now, Mr. Ueda, the days...
Nothing particularly shaky happened, right?
Ah.
The airport footage didn't shake out.
Then come in as a ninja.
Come in as a ninja.Come in as a ninja.
Do mayhem bushi
Come in Ninja
Come in as a ninja
Riotous bushido
In with the ninjas
Come in as a ninja
Do mayhem bushido
Cool.
Maybe this
This could be great.
Really?
Yeah.
Just go in as a ninja.
And then you do the mayhem bushi.
You'll lose a song.
That's true.
I mean...
more
The length of Mayhem Bushis
It's not too bad.
Also
I did it from here in
I did it from here in De De De De
Everyone can dance.
That's great.
Okay, go on, then.
Okay, here we go.
The funny championship.
In terms of lineage...
I'm a little like Miri.
At festivals.
To Setori
Please give me time to think about it.
I'm always given time to think.
No matter where we go
I always make a big cut.
And there's always nine of us.
But for the sake of space
But because of the length of the interview, usually 6 of us answer.
Yes, yes, yes.
At that time
Each member dances with a penlight of his own color
and dance.
And when they answer the questions
holding the penlight
and answer the questions.
And then the sixth and last person
After you've finished answering.
Don't play the song.
The person who was the funniest among the six
The one who was the funniest.
Let the penlight of the funniest of the six
I said.
Everyone light up.
The one with the most colors
of the song.
After the votes were cast.
Until the end of the song
dance in the center of the stage.
That's an interesting lineThat's a funny line.
Oh, wow.
What's this?
There's an idol involved.
and the song is involved
It's so great!
It's great!
Looks good.
What do you think, Mr. Ueda?
The title is good, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The title...
Let's start with the players again.
It's a title that gets the blood boiling.
Blood Boils.
Blood Boils
Scary.
Like a doklong
But it's like...
When you dance in the center
When you dance in the center.
Is that something you can handle?
Well, with spirit.
With spirit.
You can handle it?
With practice, you'll be fine.
This is kind of an interesting experiment.
It's an interesting experiment.
Just say it once.
And see what happens.
I don't know.
Once at a live show.
What's the next song?
Once you explain the rule
Yes, yes, yes.
If you decide the most.
I don't know...
I feel like we can do something.
And we can face off against other idols.
It's about time.
For a comedy competition?
With a great comedy.
So, some of them came in.
Three, three.
I'll go this way, Mr. Flioff.
I'm sure they'd be happy to do it over there.
I feel sorry for that idol.
That's nice.
This is something.
I think it's going to expand in a lot of ways.
Then...
Let's try Takanashi's idea.
Let's try it at the next show.
Yeah.
But we don't have to change much.
Just tell us the rules first.
You're really something, aren't you?
Don't change the system so much.Don't change the system so much.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Think hard.
Shall we do it then?
Let's do it.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Well, that's great, then, let's do this! So, if you're coming to the festival, I'm sure you're looking forward to it.
Well, that's all for the FesCamassian presentation!
Is it done?
We finished the first one today. How was it?
Do you have it?
I don't know who Anpanman is.
I don't know...
I can't think of any names.
You're right.
Tendon man?
It's hard to think.
It's hard to think, that's for sure.
That's why it's so hard for comedians to come up with big names.
It was a big theme, wasn't it?
Shomo's answer was interesting.
Yui's, Oedo-san is talking.
That's amazing.
I missed the last show because I was sick.
I hadn't recorded in two months, so I had to stop for the first time.
I was nervous for the first time.
Sakira's pressure was incredible.
That's for sure.
I was there last week, but I couldn't get it out.
I was there last week and I couldn't get it out.
Sorry for the slamming.
Slams are great.
We all had it at once, and I was able to do this.
Everybody got the message.
When I did it, it went viral on Twitter.
It went viral.
It's not even pretty.
How was your Halloween?
I'm...
Shonen style.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I was just about to say something before that.
The way you raised your hand was so tiny.
I couldn't guess at all.
Just that part.
And the look in your eyes, too.
And the way you raised your hands.
I want to say something, but...
I don't know what would happen if it got worse.
What if he's scared and he's not sure and he raises his hands like that?
I don't want to get stabbed.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
I've been thinking about it, but...
I'll try my best to speak more.
Let's all work hard on the second recording.
Let's do our best.
I thought it was Kimoto-san who chose the center.
because of her negativity.Because of the negativity
I was wondering if it was okay for me to keep them waiting.
Bring back as much catering as possible
I'll close quickly.
I'm going to be a little rude
I want to go home.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Today we have a pissed off version.
Hey! What's going on with the channel subscriptions?
I've been trying to subscribe to your channel, but it's not getting any subscribers.
It's not cool if it doesn't go up a little bit.
I may look like this, but I really care about it.
If you're already doing it, thank you.
If you haven't, what's wrong with you?
I'll pull your balls out and make you say, "Fuck you!
Okay, I'm going to do the last one.
I'll be right there.
Thank you!